milepoint.com 2015-06-30

# Privacy Policy | Milepoint

This Privacy Policy is offered by **_milepoint_** as an extension of our commitment to combine quality content, personal service, and additional services with integrity in dealing with our members. This Privacy Policy covers the **_milepoint_** forums and any associated content including RSS feeds, emails, newsletters, surveys, member comments, and other applications. 

This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using **_milepoint_**. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that we do not own or control, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage. 

Please also read our [Terms and Rules](http://milepoint.com/forums/help/terms). Your use of **_milepoint_** constitutes agreement to the Terms and Rules and this Privacy Policy. 

**WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**  
We collect information from you when you register on _milepoint_ , upgrade your membership, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to any surveys, fill out a form, submit information, request information or even make a post. When upgrading your membership or registering on _milepoint_ , you may be asked to enter information such as your name, email address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. As well, you may choose to visit _milepoint_ anonymously by just lurking. 

**WHAT DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION FOR?**  
Broadly speaking, any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To process transactions such as if you were to upgrade your membership level: your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the membership level requested.
  * To personalize your experience: your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.
  * To improve our site: we continually strive to improve our site offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
  * To improve customer service: your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * To send periodic emails: the email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

**HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION?**  
We implement a variety of physical, electronic, and administrative security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. 

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, mailing address, phone number, etc.) will be kept on file for more than 60 days in order to expedite and improve future visits and transactions that may occur on our site. 

**HOW DO WE SECURE YOUR INFORMATION?**   
We secure your personal information submitted by you by using reasonable efforts to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, or accidental loss or destruction of the information. Your postings on _milepoint_ and other communications you may have with us via email or regular mail may not be secure unless we advise you that security measures are in place prior to your sending information. So, if you choose to communicate with us through these means, you are assuming the risk of doing so and we request that you do not send or post sensitive information through these means. If you want to safeguard the information exchange, feel free to give us a call at (719) 597-8889. 

**DO WE USE COOKIES?**  
Yes, _milepoint_ utilizes standard technologies called “cookies” and "log files" to collect information about how milepoint is used. Cookies are very small text files saved to your computer used to track your navigation around _milepoint_. These cookies are used to track which forum posts remain unread, and whether you are a current member of milepoint and your membership level of service on _milepoint_. This cookie is not identifiable other than by the website server, and does not store any information which could disclose personal information about you. Log files are merely a record of this information. Other information gathered may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at _milepoint_ , the websites visited just before and just after _milepoint_ , what type of web browser (Internet Explorer, Chrome, Firefox, etc.) you are using, and your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address. Information is collected on an aggregate basis without any association to your personal information so that you remain anonymous. If you do not wish to transmit “cookie” information about yourself, you may turn off the cookie function in your web browser; please consult the “Help” section of your personal browser to correctly do so. 

**DO WE DISCLOSE ANY INFORMATION TO ADVERTISERS OR OUTSIDE PARTIES?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to advertisers or outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our site, so long as these outside parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce milepoint policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses — the key words here are ‘non-personally identifiable.’ 

**THIRD PARTY LINKS**  
We may include or offer third party products or services on our site. These third party websites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of _milepoint_ and welcome any feedback about these other websites. 

**ANYTHING ELSE?**  
There may be times when we may ask you to provide relevant data regarding your preferences and demographics information to answer survey questions. As in other instances, we will use this information in a non-personally identifiable manner. 

**ONE ADDITIONAL NOTE**  
When creating a member profile, you can enter as much or as little biographical information as you like. This type of private information is completely managed by you and may be edited or withdrawn at anytime, but please be aware that once made public, search engines might store the data indefinitely. 

**WHAT ABOUT MY EMAIL ADDRESS?**  
Your email privacy is absolutely our top priority, and we will never, ever, sell that information to anyone. We may however, use your email address to send the following types of messages to you: 

  * account or membership level updates
  * offers for additional services provided by MilePoint
  * requests for enrollment
  * missing password information
  * replies to customer service inquiries
  * confirmation messages
  * fulfillments of legal or regulatory disclosure requirements
  * offers from our business partners

**TERMS OF SERVICE**  
Please also visit our [Terms and Rules](http://milepoint.com/forums/help/terms) section. 

**YOUR CONSENT**  
By using milepoint, you consent to our Privacy Policy. 

**CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, post in our member communication newsletter and post in our Community forum, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on February 1, 2011 

**CONTACTING US**  
If there are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy please contact us: 

milepoint  
1930 Frequent Flyer Point  
Colorado Springs, CO 80915
